{
    "deck": "french_words",
    "description": "Top 100 most common French words",
    "question_header": "French",
    "answer_header": "English",
    "questions": {
        "question_number_0": {
            "question": "partie",
            "answer": "part",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_1": {
            "question": "histoire",
            "answer": "history",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_2": {
            "question": "chercher",
            "answer": "search",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_3": {
            "question": "seulement",
            "answer": "only",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_4": {
            "question": "police",
            "answer": "police",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_5": {
            "question": "pensais",
            "answer": "thought",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_6": {
            "question": "aide",
            "answer": "help",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_7": {
            "question": "demande",
            "answer": "request",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_8": {
            "question": "genre",
            "answer": "kind",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_9": {
            "question": "mois",
            "answer": "month",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_10": {
            "question": "fr\u00e8re",
            "answer": "brother",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_11": {
            "question": "laisser",
            "answer": "let",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_12": {
            "question": "car",
            "answer": "because",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_13": {
            "question": "mettre",
            "answer": "to put",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_14": {
            "question": "aucun",
            "answer": "no",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_15": {
            "question": "laisse",
            "answer": "leash",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_16": {
            "question": "eux",
            "answer": "them",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_17": {
            "question": "ville",
            "answer": "city",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_18": {
            "question": "chaque",
            "answer": "each",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_19": {
            "question": "parl\u00e9",
            "answer": "speak",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_20": {
            "question": "arriv\u00e9",
            "answer": "come",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_21": {
            "question": "devrait",
            "answer": "should",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_22": {
            "question": "b\u00e9b\u00e9",
            "answer": "baby",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_23": {
            "question": "longtemps",
            "answer": "long time",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_24": {
            "question": "heures",
            "answer": "hours",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_25": {
            "question": "vont",
            "answer": "will",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_26": {
            "question": "pendant",
            "answer": "while",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_27": {
            "question": "revoir",
            "answer": "meet again",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_28": {
            "question": "aucune",
            "answer": "any",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_29": {
            "question": "place",
            "answer": "square",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_30": {
            "question": "parle",
            "answer": "speak",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_31": {
            "question": "compris",
            "answer": "understood",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_32": {
            "question": "savais",
            "answer": "knew",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_33": {
            "question": "\u00e9taient",
            "answer": "were",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_34": {
            "question": "attention",
            "answer": "Warning",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_35": {
            "question": "voici",
            "answer": "here is",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_36": {
            "question": "pourrais",
            "answer": "could",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_37": {
            "question": "affaire",
            "answer": "case",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_38": {
            "question": "donner",
            "answer": "give",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_39": {
            "question": "type",
            "answer": "type",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_40": {
            "question": "leurs",
            "answer": "their",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_41": {
            "question": "donn\u00e9",
            "answer": "given",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_42": {
            "question": "train",
            "answer": "train",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_43": {
            "question": "corps",
            "answer": "body",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_44": {
            "question": "endroit",
            "answer": "place",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_45": {
            "question": "yeux",
            "answer": "eyes",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_46": {
            "question": "fa\u00e7on",
            "answer": "way",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_47": {
            "question": "\u00e9coute",
            "answer": "listen",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_48": {
            "question": "dont",
            "answer": "whose",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_49": {
            "question": "trouve",
            "answer": "find",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_50": {
            "question": "premier",
            "answer": "first",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_51": {
            "question": "perdu",
            "answer": "lost",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_52": {
            "question": "main",
            "answer": "hand",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_53": {
            "question": "premi\u00e8re",
            "answer": "first",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_54": {
            "question": "c\u00f4t\u00e9",
            "answer": "side",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_55": {
            "question": "pouvoir",
            "answer": "power",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_56": {
            "question": "vieux",
            "answer": "old",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_57": {
            "question": "sois",
            "answer": "be",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_58": {
            "question": "tiens",
            "answer": "here",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_59": {
            "question": "matin",
            "answer": "morning",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_60": {
            "question": "tellement",
            "answer": "so much",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_61": {
            "question": "enfant",
            "answer": "child",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_62": {
            "question": "point",
            "answer": "point",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_63": {
            "question": "venu",
            "answer": "came",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_64": {
            "question": "suite",
            "answer": "after",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_65": {
            "question": "pardon",
            "answer": "sorry",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_66": {
            "question": "venez",
            "answer": "come",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_67": {
            "question": "devant",
            "answer": "in front of",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_68": {
            "question": "vers",
            "answer": "towards",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_69": {
            "question": "minutes",
            "answer": "minutes",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_70": {
            "question": "demand\u00e9",
            "answer": "request",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_71": {
            "question": "chambre",
            "answer": "bedroom",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_72": {
            "question": "mis",
            "answer": "placed",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_73": {
            "question": "belle",
            "answer": "beautiful",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_74": {
            "question": "droit",
            "answer": "law",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_75": {
            "question": "aimerais",
            "answer": "would like to",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_76": {
            "question": "aujourd'hui",
            "answer": "today",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_77": {
            "question": "mari",
            "answer": "husband",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_78": {
            "question": "cause",
            "answer": "cause",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_79": {
            "question": "enfin",
            "answer": "finally",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_80": {
            "question": "esp\u00e8re",
            "answer": "hope",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_81": {
            "question": "eau",
            "answer": "water",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_82": {
            "question": "attendez",
            "answer": "Wait",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_83": {
            "question": "parti",
            "answer": "left",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_84": {
            "question": "nouvelle",
            "answer": "new",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_85": {
            "question": "boulot",
            "answer": "job",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_86": {
            "question": "arr\u00eater",
            "answer": "Stop",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_87": {
            "question": "dirait",
            "answer": "would say",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_88": {
            "question": "terre",
            "answer": "Earth",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_89": {
            "question": "compte",
            "answer": "account",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_90": {
            "question": "donne",
            "answer": "given",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_91": {
            "question": "loin",
            "answer": "far",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_92": {
            "question": "fin",
            "answer": "end",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_93": {
            "question": "croire",
            "answer": "believe",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_94": {
            "question": "ch\u00e9rie",
            "answer": "sweetheart",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_95": {
            "question": "gros",
            "answer": "large",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_96": {
            "question": "plut\u00f4t",
            "answer": "rather",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_97": {
            "question": "aura",
            "answer": "will have",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_98": {
            "question": "filles",
            "answer": "girls",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_99": {
            "question": "jouer",
            "answer": "to play",
            "know_it": 0
        },
        "question_number_100": {
            "question": "bureau",
            "answer": "office",
            "know_it": 0
        }
    }
}